The invocation by our marchief.
Everybody, Father, we're thankful for you.
We're thankful for this.
Is that saying you got this meeting tonight?
You are a council wisdom, and they make decisions.
Amen.
We're pleased to invite the United States and America.
And to the Republic for which it stands,
one nation under God, individual,
and there's the United States.
Public input.
That's good.
The first one.
This Francis dog.
We have a situation here in my arm.
The only effect is four people.
If you need help with your utilities,
and you go to salvation on me,
salvation on me,
forwards.
A deal to the city saying,
we will pay this bill.
There's much of this bill.
The only problem is they don't get to the letter one.
It's a person who has the electric bill.
It's a pain in the light,
because it's a promissory note.
It's not an act of a deal.
And I'm asking if that's the change.
If the promissory note is just as good as cash on hand,
that way people who are trying to get help
and trying to keep up to date on the bills
aren't getting snacked in the next month,
because they were light.
Yeah.
We get your name and number,
and we have it here.
So watch my reach out to you.
Okay.
All right.
Thank you for coming.
Claims list.
Motion approved.
Hi.
Jones.
This is a bottle of claim for Pinscola G.R.R.
Realizing the associated claim for proceedings
around $915.
Yes, the board.
This is for the claim for $915.
If it is paid, which I guess is the real machine.
If it is paid that we'll have a remaining bounce of $384,106.
$79 for the year.
Was this for the tell hole?
No, that's not just.
I can maybe get lucky.
No. Motion to approve. Second.
So, aye.
E. Step. Aye.
Jones. Aye. Farms. Aye.
I.
Perfect. Aye.
So, I don't know if there's a minute.
The rhythm is possible.
This agenda.
Eight trustee meeting.
An ounce.
Nine adjourn.
Motion.
Second.
So, hold it.
Jones. Aye. Farms. Aye. E. Step.
Aye.